{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 96, "endOffset": 104, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 13, "endOffset": 24, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 62, "endOffset": 74, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 5, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 38, "endOffset": 47, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Oscars 2023: Jimmy Kimmel roasts THAT Will Smith Oscars slap, Nicole Kidman's AMC deal and ribs Hollywood's obsession with weight loss drug  in epic monologue"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 8, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 153, "endOffset": 158, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Lady Gaga goes bare! Superstar takes off her make-up and changes into jeans and T-shirt for stripped down performance of nominated track Hold My Hand at Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 15, "endOffset": 29, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 9, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 77, "endOffset": 82, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Hugh Grant and Andie MacDowell have a Four Weddings And A Funeral reunion at Oscars 2023... as he makes a crude joke about his appearance"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 144, "endOffset": 156, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 5, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 130, "endOffset": 138, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Oscars 2023 recap: Everything Everywhere All at Once wins SEVEN Awards including Best Picture: Brendan Fraser bags Best Actor for The Whale and Michelle Yeoh wins Best Actress"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 44, "endOffset": 56, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'We will always remain hopelessly devoted': John Travolta breaks down in tears as he introduces In Memoriam segment after death of beloved Grease co-star Olivia Newton-John"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 53, "endOffset": 65, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 153, "endOffset": 158, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Dramatic shawls, enormous ruffles, and TRENCH COATS: Florence Pugh, Zoe Saldana, Laverne Cox and Lilly Singh lead the list of worst dressed stars at the Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 62, "endOffset": 78, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 132, "endOffset": 137, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Olivia Wilde flashes her black bralet in revealing gown while Jennifer Coolidge stuns in figure-hugging ensemble at the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 142, "endOffset": 147, "displayName": "ORG"}], "textContent": "Dealing with dry, cracked heels? Say goodbye to foot calluses with this satisfyingly gross £14 foot peel that's had over 116 million views on TikTok"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 138, "endOffset": 143, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Emily Blunt is the picture of elegance in a white figure-hugging gown as she poses for a slew of playful snaps with Dwayne Johnson at the Oscars 2023"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 53, "endOffset": 65, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'She is so p***** off!': Dancing on Ice viewers spot Vanessa Bauer looking 'furious' with partner Joey Essex after coming second to Nile Wilson"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 131, "endOffset": 140, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 37, "endOffset": 45, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 76, "endOffset": 81, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Nobody's looking at your Poker Face! Lady Gaga parades tattooed backside at Oscars 2023 in a VERY racy sheer dress just days after Gigi Hadid wore it on Versace catwalk"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 15, "endOffset": 33, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 95, "endOffset": 100, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "That's my boy! Julia Louis-Dreyfus is one proud mom as she takes son Henry Hall as her date to Oscars 2023"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 14, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 126, "endOffset": 131, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Andrew Garfield cuts a dapper figure as he graces the red carpet before taking to the stage to present TWO awards at the 2023 Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 99, "endOffset": 112, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 11, "endOffset": 21, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Tie me up! Rooney Mara wears unusual tulle gown with knot in train on champagne-coloured carpet at Academy Awards 2023"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 102, "endOffset": 114, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 13, "endOffset": 26, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 5, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Oscars 2023: Morgan Freeman wears a satin glove on his paralyzed hand as he presents at ceremony with Margot Robbie - 15 years after car accident"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 45, "endOffset": 50, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Paul Mescal nails his red carpet look at the Oscars 2023 in a white tuxedo with a red rose following his nomination for Best Actor"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 111, "endOffset": 116, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Cara Delevingne puts on a VERY leggy display in an eye-catching red gown with a daring thigh-high split at the Oscars 2023"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 16, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 115, "endOffset": 120, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Jennifer Coolidge looks every inch the blonde bombshell in form-hugging silk black gown as she attends Vanity Fair Oscars Party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 8, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Why the Oscars red carpet has changed colour to champagne for the 2023 ceremony"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 127, "endOffset": 139, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 14, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Gabrielle Union takes the plunge in black Ralph Lauren floor-length gown with deep neckline at 2023 Vanity Fair Oscar Party in Beverly Hills"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 87, "endOffset": 100, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 75, "endOffset": 80, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Margot Robbie puts on busty display in off-the-shoulder gown to present at Oscars with Morgan Freeman - but skips the red carpet after being snubbed in Best Actress category"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "The Last Of Us finale: The harrowing birth of Ellie is revealed while Joel does whatever it takes to protect her... including telling her a horrific lie"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 113, "endOffset": 126, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 29, "endOffset": 41, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Sealed with a (sloppy) kiss! Nicole Kidman and husband Keith Urban pack on the PDA as they share a smooch on the Academy Awards red carpet"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 41, "endOffset": 46, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Michelle Yeoh stuns on the red carpet at Oscars 2023 in white gown as she's nominated for Best Actress for Everything Everywhere All at Once"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 80, "endOffset": 85, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "A dream in tangerine! Janelle Monae brings her fresh and fun sense of glamor to Oscars 2023 in black crop top and bright skirt"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 17, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 62, "endOffset": 67, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Andrea Riseborough is supported by partner Karim Saleh on the Oscars 2023 red carpet amid controversy over her Best Actress nomination"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 116, "endOffset": 121, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Kate Hudson is a dazzling diva as she models a jaw-dropping jeweled mermaid gown and blonde bombshell waves for her Oscars 2023 red carpet arrival"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Dancing On Ice Final 2023 RECAP: Nile Wilson is crowned the winner! After going head-to-head with Joey Essex to skate the Bolero"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 114, "endOffset": 125, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Justin Bieber declares his love for his wife Hailey as she cuddles him in her bikini in sweet vacation snaps amid Selena Gomez 'feud'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 110, "endOffset": 115, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "All Quiet on the Western Front screenwriter Lesley Paterson turns heads in a neon yellow and pink gown on the Oscars 2023 red carpet"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Love Island 2023: Casey looks put out as Rosie reveals her bombshell co-star Keanan Brand has since slid into her DM's as the pair appear on Aftersun"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 46, "endOffset": 50, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 17, "endOffset": 32, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 88, "endOffset": 93, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Siren in silver! Jessica Chastain wears busty Gucci dress with dramatic velvet train to Oscars 2023"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 16, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 127, "endOffset": 132, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Michelle Williams brings the sparkle in shimmering white gown and sheer cape as she poses with husband Thomas Kail at the 2023 Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 89, "endOffset": 97, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 28, "endOffset": 33, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Melissa McCarthy sizzles at Oscars 2023 in a red-hot Christian Siriano gown as she joins Hollywood's biggest stars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 97, "endOffset": 101, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 106, "endOffset": 111, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Austin Butler smolders in a chic black tuxedo before learning the fate of his Best Actor nod for Elvis at Oscars - and why he DIDN'T bring  Kaia Gerber as his date"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 124, "endOffset": 129, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Phoebe Waller-Bridge exhibits her svelte waist in a black lace corset gown as she makes a rare red carpet appearance at the Oscars 2023"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 43, "endOffset": 50, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 98, "endOffset": 106, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 83, "endOffset": 88, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Elizabeth Olsen brings sexy back in slinky Givenchy halter gown as she attends the Oscars 2023 in Hollywood"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 44, "endOffset": 49, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Guillermo del Toro wins first award at 2023 Oscars ceremony for Pinocchio and dedicates win to 'love of my life' wife Kim"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 42, "endOffset": 55, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 141, "endOffset": 146, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Step back in time! Best actress favourite Cate Blanchett covers up in unique turquoise and black Eighties-inspired Louis Vuitton gown at the Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 9, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 118, "endOffset": 123, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Idris Elba, 49, is joined by his glamorous wife Sabrina, 33, as she stuns in a figure-hugging green satin gown at the Oscars 2023"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 17, "endOffset": 25, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Love Island host Maya Jama accidentally reveals the dumped couple BEFORE it's aired as she makes giant gaffe in Aftersun advert and on Instagram"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Love Island's Will and Jessie are DUMPED from the villa just a day before the finale as the four final couples are revealed"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 90, "endOffset": 103, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 19, "endOffset": 34, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Sensational at 64! Jamie Lee Curtis looks elegant in beaded gown alongside her husband at Academy Awards and jokes about her life goals now she's 'old'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 16, "endOffset": 21, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 24, "endOffset": 33, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Banned from the Oscars: Will Smith takes his family to see life coach guru after being forced to give up honor of presenting best actor after THAT  slap"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 28, "endOffset": 41, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 86, "endOffset": 91, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Ana de Armas pays homage to Marilyn Monroe again in shimmering silver mermaid gown on Oscars red carpet... as she is nominated for Best Actress"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 17, "endOffset": 25, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Love Island host Maya Jama puts on a busty display in a colourful sequin mini dress during Aftersun in South Africa - after accidentally revealing the dumped couple"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 99, "endOffset": 104, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Halle Berry exudes Grecian glamour in a rose-adorned white gown with VERY racy thigh-split at 2023 Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 23, "endOffset": 39, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Top Gun: Maverick star Jennifer Connelly hits the Oscar red carpet with 19-year-old son Stellan as her blockbuster sequel is up for Best Picture"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 5, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 13, "endOffset": 23, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Oscars 2023: Salma Hayek sizzles in burnt orange sequin gown with glitzy train as she hits the red carpet"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 63, "endOffset": 68, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Kerry Condon stuns in a strapless yellow gown as she walks the Oscars 2023 red carpet after being tipped to win Best Supporting Actress"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 39, "endOffset": 44, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Angela Bassett, 64, looks regal at the Oscars 2023 in a violet Moschino gown as she's nominated for Best Supporting Actress"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 12, "endOffset": 22, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "When is the Love Island 2023 final? Who will win? What is the prize? Everything you need to know..."}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 112, "endOffset": 125, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Oti Mabuse puts on a busty display in a custom corset with over 20,000 Swarovski crystals as she arrives at the Dancing On Ice Final"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 40, "endOffset": 45, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "What REALLY happened between Meghan and Fergie? After Sarah said she 'hadn't met' Harry's wife, inside their relationship"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 70, "endOffset": 78, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Magician David Blaine has separated shoulder popped into place during Las Vegas show and CONTINUES ON in performance"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 23, "endOffset": 27, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 49, "endOffset": 54, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Zoe Saldana slips into Fendi couture gown at the Oscars 2023 alongside her husband Marco Perego Saldana"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 51, "endOffset": 56, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Golden girl! Sigourney Weaver, 73, glitters on the Oscars 2023 red carpet in sparkling gown"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 138, "endOffset": 143, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Antonio Banderas looks handsome in slick tuxedo while girlfriend Nicole Kimpel wows in fiery cropped look with feathered coat at the 2023 Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Katie Price fans are left saying the same thing as they all spot one detail after she posted a new selfie"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Dancing On Ice 2023: Sobbing Nile is crowned the WINNER in grand final after his emotional Bolero - beating out Joey Essex and The Vivienne"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 130, "endOffset": 135, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Elton John, 75, dons a bejewelled suit and quirky heart shaped glasses as he joins dapper husband David Furnish, 60 at his annual Oscars bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 105, "endOffset": 113, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 95, "endOffset": 100, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Dripping in jewels! Fan Bingbing looks regal in a plunging silver and emerald gown at the 2023 Oscars in Hollywood"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 14, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 122, "endOffset": 127, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Andie MacDowell and her look-alike daughter Rainey Qualley exude elegance in form-fitting black gowns while attending the Oscars 2023"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 126, "endOffset": 131, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Sandra Oh, 51, exudes elegance in a bold orange gown with a plunging neckline and glamorous batwing sleeves as she graces the Oscars red carpet"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 78, "endOffset": 83, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "She did the thing! Ariana DeBose dazzles in plunging thigh-split gown at 2023 Oscars - after THAT viral BAFTAS rap"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 75, "endOffset": 80, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Monica Barbaro flashes her cleavage  in a racy blue and maroon gown at the Oscars as she supports her blockbuster film Top Gun: Maverick"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 118, "endOffset": 122, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 65, "endOffset": 70, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Hope he has security! Baz Luhrmann wears a $263k necklace to the Oscars and is supported by his wife and daughter as  Elvis is up for several awards"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 33, "endOffset": 38, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Winnie Harlow is a vision at the Oscars 2023 in a sleeveless canary yellow dress as she struts down the champagne carpet"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 107, "endOffset": 112, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Mindy Kaling's disappearing act: Comedian looks thinner than ever after losing more than 40lbs as she hits Oscars 2023 red carpet in Vera Wang"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 37, "endOffset": 38, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 46, "endOffset": 51, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Wonder Woman director Patty Jenkins SLAMS the Oscars for nominating no female directors this year: 'I give up'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 57, "endOffset": 62, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Sofia Carson looks divine in white princess gown at 2023 Oscars... ahead of performing her nominated song Applause with Diane Warren"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 90, "endOffset": 95, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "The Little Mermaid star Halle Bailey wows in powder blue princess gown as she attends the Oscars 2023"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 98, "endOffset": 103, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 81, "endOffset": 89, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Brendan Fraser looks dapper in black tuxedo as he's nominated for Best Actor for The Whale at the Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 128, "endOffset": 141, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 32, "endOffset": 40, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Hong Chau, who is nominated for The Whale, is the picture of elegance in a pink gown with a black train as she attends the 95th Academy Awards"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 54, "endOffset": 59, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Vanessa Hudgens is a modern-day Audrey Hepburn at the Oscars in a black-and-white  gown as she flashes her engagement ring from Cole Tucker"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 37, "endOffset": 47, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "'Isaac Newton has been quiet since': Love Island's Ron is left baffled after Lana said birds 'don't have any GRAVITY'... leaving fans in hysterics"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 121, "endOffset": 126, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Jenna Dewan shows off her dancer's legs in a strappy black dress as she joins fiancé Steve Kazee at the Night Before the Oscars fundraiser"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 39, "endOffset": 49, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "'Someone has finally called her out!': Love Island viewers rejoice as Shaq's sister confronts Tanya over her Casa Amor kiss with Martin"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 55, "endOffset": 67, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 81, "endOffset": 89, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 21, "endOffset": 33, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 36, "endOffset": 49, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Getting Oscar ready! Kate Bosworth, Kim Kardashian and Florence Pugh prepare for Hollywood's big night with treatments and workouts"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 33, "endOffset": 43, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "'Their relationship is so vain': Love Island viewers accuse Tom of being with Samie for her looks as he ONLY describes her as 'stunning'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 15, "endOffset": 28, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 9, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Kat Graham and Erica Pelosini coordinate in animal prints at Chopard's pre-Oscar party in Bel-Air"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 21, "endOffset": 26, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Laverne Cox stuns at Oscars 2023 in a vintage Vera Wang gown with sultry black sleeves and a show-stopping turquoise train"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 63, "endOffset": 68, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 143, "endOffset": 152, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Jimmy Kimmel jokes this year's champagne-colored carpet at the Oscars means 'no blood will be shed' during tonight's ceremony - after infamous Will Smith slap"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 4, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 46, "endOffset": 54, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Adele 'is set to extend her hugely successful Las Vegas residency after being offered £1million per NIGHT to perform more shows'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Love Island viewers all saying the same thing as 'cringey' Ron keeps calling girlfriend Lana 'my Mrs' during 'meet the parents' episode"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 98, "endOffset": 111, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Angela Bassett sips on extra large Dunkin' Donuts iced coffee as she gets glammed up for the 2023 Academy Awards"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 48, "endOffset": 50, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 32, "endOffset": 43, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Alastair Campbell's support for Gary Lineker in BBC debate is 'tainted' by their commercial podcast links, critics say"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 78, "endOffset": 94, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 61, "endOffset": 73, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'She's perfect!' Joey Essex gushes about rumoured girlfriend Vanessa Bauer as Phillip Schofield says the star has a 'friend for life' after the couple placed second"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 116, "endOffset": 128, "displayName": "FAC"}, {"startOffset": 133, "endOffset": 143, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 97, "endOffset": 102, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Ashley Graham puts on a busty display in a sheer black gown with dramatic sleeves as she attends Oscars 2023 at the Dolby Theatre in Los Angeles"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 2, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 99, "endOffset": 107, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 83, "endOffset": 93, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "BBC planning 'spin-off for smash hit show The Traitors ahead of second season with Rylan Clark and Judi Love eyed as hosts'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 46, "endOffset": 57, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Jurassic Park stars Ariana Richards, 43, and  Joe Mazzello, 39, reunite 30 years after starring in the blockbuster movie"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 75, "endOffset": 77, "displayName": "ORG"}], "textContent": "BRENDAN O'NEILL: If a celebrity in a tantrum were to get the better of the BBC we would all lose out"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 61, "endOffset": 63, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Billie Piper gets into character for her latest role playing BBC producer Sam McAllister in Scoop  - portraying the shocking Prince Andrew interview"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Meryl Streep takes the spotlight as she joins the all-star cast of Only Murders In The Building in new season three teaser: 'Oh, it's me!'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 53, "endOffset": 66, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 81, "endOffset": 83, "displayName": "ORG"}], "textContent": "'You can't say he doesn't have an unfair advantage!' Dancing On Ice viewers slam ITV show for being 'fixed' as Nile Wilson is crowned winner in final"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 71, "endOffset": 84, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 17, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Ekin-Su Culculoglu slips back into her sheer catsuit as she returns to Dancing On Ice to recreate THAT sexy Toxic routine"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 54, "endOffset": 66, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Cara Delevingne and girlfriend Minke grab dinner with Sienna Miller and Matt Smith - after model reflected on struggles in Vogue interview"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 17, "endOffset": 31, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 139, "endOffset": 148, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Love Island star Claudia Fogarty sends temperatures soaring in a satin bralet and an oversized blazer as she heads to a Chris Brown gig in Manchester"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 8, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Demi Rose puts her curves on display in a skimpy orange bikini while revealing she is working out five times a week (and sometimes TWICE a day!)"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 33, "endOffset": 43, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 138, "endOffset": 146, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'You're not here for a holiday!' Love Island's Olivia Hawkins reveals cast were told off for taking secret naps... after being shushed by Maya Jama"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 97, "endOffset": 110, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 27, "endOffset": 42, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'I'm so excited!': Beaming Holly Willoughby looks sensational in a plunging silver gown ahead of Dancing On Ice's grand final"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 41, "endOffset": 54, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Jimmy Kimmel gives a preview of the 2023 Academy Awards white carpet ahead of his hosting duties: 'Happy Oscar Sunday!'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 8, "endOffset": 21, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Who won Dancing On Ice 2023? Nile Wilson is crowned champion after beating Joey Essex to first place following a Bolero dance off"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 126, "endOffset": 138, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 102, "endOffset": 107, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Kevin Bacon, 64, looks sharp as he puts his arm around wife of 34 years Kyra Sedgwick, 57, at the Pre-Oscars Awards dinner in Beverly Hills"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 62, "endOffset": 63, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "'This is just a popularity contest!': Dancing on Ice viewers SLAM 'unfair' voting after lines open before any of the finalists have even skated"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 12, "endOffset": 20, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Scary good! Scream VI sets a new franchise record at the box office after earning a whopping $44.5 million domestically in its opening weekend"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 66, "endOffset": 68, "displayName": "ORG"}], "textContent": "How mum's breakdown taught me the healing power of a tidy house:  BBC decluttering guru DILLY CARTER found solace in making order"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 8, "endOffset": 21, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Who are Dancing On Ice winners Nile Wilson and Olivia Smart? A look at the lives of the TWO Olympians"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 40, "endOffset": 53, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 61, "endOffset": 76, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 140, "endOffset": 141, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 82, "endOffset": 98, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'Someone hasn't laced up their boots!': Dancing On Ice hosts Holly Willoughby and Phillip Schofield scramble to fill time after one star is LATE"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Anna Kendrick rocks leather pants for shoot at South by Southwest Festival to promote her movie Self Reliance"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 106, "endOffset": 111, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 27, "endOffset": 41, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 15, "endOffset": 24, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 47, "endOffset": 54, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Nicole Kidman, Lily James, Kristen Stewart and Rita Ora bring the glitz and glamour as they lead stars at Chanel and Charles Pre-Oscar Awards dinner"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 39, "endOffset": 49, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'I'm going to bring it back!' Bankrupt Katie Price reveals her plans to re-launch own magazine... after dodging court hearing for the FOURTH time"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 15, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Kirsty Gallacher reveals how she 'was a wreck' after her divorce,  - DR MAX PEMBERTON explains how to support loved ones dealing with the breakdown of marriage"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 81, "endOffset": 82, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 17, "endOffset": 22, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Don't rain on my Oscars parade! Clean up crews brace for MORE torrential rain in LA that could turn this year's champagne carpet into a quagmire"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 8, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 50, "endOffset": 55, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Lady Gaga 'WILL be performing Hold My Hand at the Oscars'... after it was announced she would not be singing at ceremony due to film commitment"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 41, "endOffset": 53, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "'I am thrilled!' Shannen Doherty, 51, of Beverly Hills, 90210 fame reveals getting a cosmetic procedure while battling cancer has given her a 'boost'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 16, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Kristin Cavallari throws shade at mum-shamers by flaunting her stunning figure in a skimpy string bikini while on vacation in Sweden"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Dennis Quaid, 65, looks dapper on the red carpet as he returns to his native Texas to debut his latest film The Long Game alongside wife Laura Savoie, 30"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Drew Barrymore's ex-husband Will Kopelman, 44, and wife Alexandra Michler, 33, are seen since for the first time since announcing they are expecting first child"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 53, "endOffset": 66, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Glenn Close, 75, PULLS OUT of presenting at the 95th Academy Awards after testing positive for Covid"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 44, "endOffset": 54, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "'I was 30 seconds from bleeding to death!': Love Island's Ellie Spence reveals horrifying accident that left her leg 'completely ripped off'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 4, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Elvis Presley's 'lost' 1962 red Lockheed JetStar arrives in Florida after being  abandoned in the desert for 40 years"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 8, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Kym Marsh puts on a VERY leggy display in a shimmering black dress with a daring thigh-high split as she poses for sizzling snaps"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 83, "endOffset": 87, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Can't help falling in love! As Austin Butler eyes the coveted Best Actor Oscar for Elvis, FEMAIL reveals his star-studded relationship history"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 78, "endOffset": 82, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 20, "endOffset": 33, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Razzie Awards 2023: Marilyn Monroe biopic Blonde is named Worst Picture while Elvis and Morbius also pick up multiple gongs"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 16, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 77, "endOffset": 89, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 117, "endOffset": 122, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 59, "endOffset": 74, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Leonardo DiCaprio parties with the likes of Austin Butler, Robert Pattinson, Michelle Yeoh and more A-listers at pre-Oscars bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 14, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Priyanka Chopra reveals she 'cried' to husband Nick Jonas after she was told she wasn't 'sample-sized': 'I was hurt'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 8, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 12, "endOffset": 24, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Gogglebox's Sandra Martin reveals she was 'paid more than anyone else' on the show because she was on benefits - before blowing all her earnings"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 32, "endOffset": 44, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 85, "endOffset": 90, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "'Look who decided to turn up!': Florence Pugh has a spot appear on her face ahead of Oscars 2023 as she prepares to glam up for the red carpet"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 43, "endOffset": 56, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "'It will make a difference to the result': Dancing On Ice bosses shake-up the final with new challenge that could crown winner"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 14, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Christina Ricci regrets posing in pink lingerie at age 19 on the cover of Rolling Stone: 'Not great'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 111, "endOffset": 124, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Producer of Oscar-nominated Triangle of Sadness pays heartfelt tribute to star Charlbi Dean ahead of tonight's Academy Awards after she died aged 32"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 5, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 86, "endOffset": 87, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Eminem wears a flashy gold chain  as he attends  Jimmy Iovine's 70th birthday bash in LA alongside Naomi Campbell and Elton John"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 12, "endOffset": 24, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "New grandad Ronan Keating looks bleary-eyed as he leaves his 46th birthday celebrations with wife Storm - after son Jack welcomed first child"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 4, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 60, "endOffset": 69, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Lizzo sports Yitty shirt with $1,300 Tommy Hilfiger coat in Manchester with boyfriend Myke Wright"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 72, "endOffset": 77, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Frock horror! FEMAIL reveals the most bizarre outfits to ever grace the Oscars red carpet - from cheetah print bikinis to multicolored 'bat wings'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Katie Price shows off results of her 16th boob job in skimpy bikini on her paradise Thailand holiday"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 9, "endOffset": 22, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "How will The Last Of Us end? Video game's dramatic conclusion reveals crucial clues about how the upcoming season finale could play out"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 12, "endOffset": 20, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 103, "endOffset": 111, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 77, "endOffset": 82, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "How good IS Brad Pitt's $310-a-bottle champagne? Sommelier puts the official Oscars bubbly made by the Hollywood star to the test"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Mick Jagger, 79, dons blue 'DILF' cap to watch his beloved Arsenal at football match with his sons Deveraux, 6, and Lucas, 22"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 132, "endOffset": 137, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Tallia Storm shows off her incredible figure in skimpy black bikini as she takes a mirror selfie while enjoying workout and swim in London"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 118, "endOffset": 131, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 56, "endOffset": 68, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Oscar weekend! Actress Blanca Blanco checks out the new Beverly Hills hotel The Maybourne where stars stay during the Academy Awards"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 72, "endOffset": 73, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Tom Sandoval is missing from his friend Tom Schwartz's karaoke night in LA... after cheating scandal with Raquel Leviss rocked Vanderpump Rules"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 111, "endOffset": 113, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Jenna Ortega shows a hint of tummy in a crop top that she pairs with a striped suit as she heads to a party in NYC after hosting Saturday Night Live"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 111, "endOffset": 112, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Naomi Campbell cuts a stylish figure in a white shirt and figure-hugging corset as she leaves private party in LA"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 155, "endOffset": 160, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Ready for a Wilde night! Olivia flashes her black bralette in daring ensemble as Julia Garner and Emily Ratajkowski dazzle in sheer outfits at Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 14, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 61, "endOffset": 66, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 149, "endOffset": 155, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 129, "endOffset": 138, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Andrew Garfield becomes a meme AGAIN! Star's awkward grin at Oscars  goes viral - one year after actor's blase texting snap post-Will Smith slap set Twitter alight"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 15, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 137, "endOffset": 142, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Jessica Chastain is praised by social media users for being one of the only celebrities wearing a mask while sitting indoors at the 2023 Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 101, "endOffset": 114, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 8, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "How the Oscars 2023 became the year of the comeback: Veteran actors and tales of redemption dominate Academy Awards ceremony, writes ALISON BOSHOFF"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 144, "endOffset": 152, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 128, "endOffset": 133, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Ready for a Wilde night! Olivia flashes black bralette in revealing gown as she leads the glamorous arrivals at the Vanity Fair Oscars party in Hollywood"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 106, "endOffset": 111, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 30, "endOffset": 37, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Still in the honeymoon phase! Rita Ora wears bridal white and kisses husband Taika Waititi at Vanity Fair Oscars party... three months after confirming nuptials"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 4, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 92, "endOffset": 97, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Elvis Presley's granddaughter Riley Keough slips into a slinky sequin dress for Vanity Fair Oscars Party with husband Ben Smith-Petersen"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 16, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 127, "endOffset": 135, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 106, "endOffset": 111, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Donatella Versace, 67, flaunts her smooth visage and stunning frame wearing a shimmering gold gown at the Oscars party in West Hollywood"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 78, "endOffset": 84, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 157, "endOffset": 169, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Tracee Ellis Ross is a fearless fashionista as she poses up in a black velvet Balmain catsuit and a chic wide-brimmed hat for the Vanity Fair Oscar Party in Beverly Hills"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 115, "endOffset": 124, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 96, "endOffset": 109, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 46, "endOffset": 57, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 155, "endOffset": 160, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Emily Ratajkowski almost frees the nipple and Kylie Jenner vies for attention in busty frock as Kendall Jenner and Gigi Hadid KISS at Vanity Fair's A-list Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 138, "endOffset": 146, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 122, "endOffset": 127, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Ready for a Wilde night! Olivia flashes bralette in revealing gown as she leads the glamorous arrivals at the Vanity Fair Oscars party in Hollywood"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 4, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 85, "endOffset": 93, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 21, "endOffset": 26, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "How Chris Rock spent Oscars night one year after THAT explosive slap: Comedian shuns Hollywood in favor of quiet viewing party in Florida"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 9, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 107, "endOffset": 123, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Gigi Hadid is red hot in an off-shoulder skintight gown at the Vanity Fair Oscar Party... after reigniting Leonardo DiCaprio romance rumors"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 126, "endOffset": 131, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Julia Garner rocks a sultry black dress with avant-garde tire collar as she poses with husband Mark Foster at the Vanity Fair Oscars Party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 8, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 41, "endOffset": 52, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 72, "endOffset": 80, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 59, "endOffset": 65, "displayName": "ORG"}], "textContent": "Fury at BBC for humiliating climbdown as Gary Lineker wins Twitter row: Tim Davie apologises and invites the host back to Match of the Day"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 32, "endOffset": 43, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 15, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 124, "endOffset": 129, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Malala Yousafzai responds after Jimmy Kimmel was branded a 'national disgrace' for 'harassing' Taliban shooting survivor at Oscars with jokes"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 41, "endOffset": 50, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 12, "endOffset": 23, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 53, "endOffset": 60, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 66, "endOffset": 76, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Bleary-eyed Olivia Wilde joins glamorous Lily James, Rita Ora and Salma Hayek as leading the stars heading home after a night partying at Vanity Fair bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 7, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Euphoria star Hunter Schafer ensures all eyes are on her as she dares to bare in a bandeau top and pearlescent skirt"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 126, "endOffset": 132, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 136, "endOffset": 141, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 9, "endOffset": 15, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Pregnant Rihanna flaunts her bump in a for her FOURTH tum-flashing outfit of the night as she and A$AP Rocky lead arrivals at Beyoncé's Oscars bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 47, "endOffset": 57, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 17, "endOffset": 25, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'The boy lied!': Maya Jama is left in shock as Love Island's Will and Casey become embroiled in row on Aftersun with the farmer calling his pal a 'snake'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 39, "endOffset": 49, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'I will always be there to guide her': Katie Price predicts daughter Princess, 15, will be a 'successful model' - after signing four-figure contract with PLT"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 36, "endOffset": 40, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 16, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Priscilla Presley is 'locked out of Elvis's Graceland mansion by granddaughter Riley Keough who changed the locks on the doors after she contested Lisa Marie's $35million will'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 10, "endOffset": 19, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 135, "endOffset": 148, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Who is in Demi Moore's inner circle? Actress, 60, reveals who her famous friends are during Oscar viewing party... after cozying up to Sandra Bullock"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 55, "endOffset": 67, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Colin Farrell introduces his son Henry Tadeusz, 13, to Nicole Kidman and his The Banshees Of Inisherin co-star Brendan Gleeson"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 89, "endOffset": 99, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 56, "endOffset": 68, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 23, "endOffset": 28, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Inside the Vanity Fair Oscars party: Brendan Fraser and Michelle Yeoh compare awards and Ke Huy Quan tucks into a burger as the celebrations"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Eamonn Holmes is supported by his doting wife Ruth Langsford as he reveals he's focused on 'regaining his balance' while issuing a health update"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 98, "endOffset": 103, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Iris Law cuts an edgy figure in khaki one shoulder dress with hood as she attends the Vanity Fair Oscars Party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 105, "endOffset": 110, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Florence + The Machine singer Florence Welch casts a spell in flowing gown during mesmerising concert at Sydney's Qudos Bank Arena"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 15, "endOffset": 26, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 96, "endOffset": 107, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 9, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 116, "endOffset": 124, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Ian Wright and Alan Shearer WON'T face punishment for boycotting Match of the Day in support of Gary Lineker, after Tim Davie apologised"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 42, "endOffset": 57, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 139, "endOffset": 144, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "'This is the nepo baby's truest revenge': Jamie Lee Curtis sends the internet wild as she points out that her movie star parents never won Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 85, "endOffset": 90, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Megan Fox puts on a VERY busty display in a plunging gown as she attends Vanity Fair Oscars bash without beau Machine Gun Kelly amid troubled romance"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Paris Jackson is the epitome of glamour as she stuns in a black ruffled tulle gown while showcasing her tattoos at the Vanity Fair Oscar Party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 102, "endOffset": 110, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 116, "endOffset": 122, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Naatu Naatu from Telugu-language movie RRR becomes first Indian film song to win an Oscar as it beats Lady Gaga and Rihanna to top prize"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 125, "endOffset": 130, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Kylie Jenner takes fans inside the most star-studded party of the year as she shares behind-the-scenes videos of Vanity Fair Oscars bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 62, "endOffset": 65, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 98, "endOffset": 105, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "A fairytale wedding! Princess Iman of Jordan is dazzling in a Dior gown as she ties the knot with New York based financier in lavish ceremony"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 9, "endOffset": 15, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Pregnant Rihanna exposes her baby bump in an emerald green shawl as proud partner A$AP Rocky leans in for a backstage kiss"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 41, "endOffset": 52, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 100, "endOffset": 115, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 125, "endOffset": 130, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "'One of the worst things I've ever seen' Jimmy Kimmel branded a 'national disgrace for 'harassing'  Malala Yousafzai at 2023 Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 81, "endOffset": 90, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 144, "endOffset": 149, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 93, "endOffset": 105, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Cara Delevingne stuns in an ivory gown as she leads British glamour with elegant Lily James, Sienna Miller and Daisy Edgar-Jones at Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 92, "endOffset": 105, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 127, "endOffset": 132, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Cate Blanchett bucks the trend and wears the same custom Louis Vuitton ensemble to both the Academy Awards and the Vanity Fair Oscars Party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 86, "endOffset": 97, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 140, "endOffset": 145, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "The award for the raciest dress goes to... Emily Ratajkowski, Alessandra Ambrosio and Olivia Wilde bare all as a parade of risque looks hit Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 129, "endOffset": 140, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 149, "endOffset": 154, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Emily In Paris star Lucien Laviscount says 'f*** the Tories' and sticks his middle finger up to the camera as he's quizzed about Gary Lineker row at Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 139, "endOffset": 147, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Heidi Klum, 49, puts on a VERY leggy display in a quirky yellow mini dress before slipping into a plunging green gown as party hops around Hollywood"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 58, "endOffset": 69, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 34, "endOffset": 46, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "She must be telling a good story! Sienna Miller enthralls Sharon Stone, Sarah Paulson and Holland Taylor during VERY animated chat at Vanity Fair bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 140, "endOffset": 148, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 91, "endOffset": 96, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "The last hurrah? James Corden cuts a dapper figure alongside wife Julia at the Vanity Fair Oscars party - as they prepare to say goodbye to Hollywood"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 71, "endOffset": 76, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Kate Hudson is forced to correct reporter who makes big mistake at the Oscars on the champagne carpet"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 135, "endOffset": 140, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Billie Eilish, 21, and her boyfriend Jesse Rutherford, 31, hold hands as they share sweet moments on the red carpet at the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 51, "endOffset": 56, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Malala's glittering red carpet tribute: Activist's Oscars jewels belonged to Afghan Queen who advocated for women's rights"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 12, "endOffset": 22, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "What is the Love Island 2023 prize money? How much will the winners  make? Will the 'Split or Steal' twist return?"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 121, "endOffset": 126, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Model Shanina Shaik looks elegant in a black gown as she holds hands with beau Matthew Adesuyan while heading to Jay-Z's Oscars afterparty"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 76, "endOffset": 86, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 16, "endOffset": 24, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Who is the REAL Maya Jama? As she wins rave reviews for her first series as Love Island host, how presenter overcame family turmoil and living off £1 dinners"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 40, "endOffset": 50, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Still each other's type on paper! Which Love Island couples are still together? From Molly-Mae Hague and Tommy Fury to Tasha Ghouri and Andrew Le Page"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Halle Berry puts on a VERY leggy display in a sheer netted dress as she heads home hand-in-hand with boyfriend Van Hunt after attending Vanity Fair bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 116, "endOffset": 121, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Suki Waterhouse dazzles in a backless sequin gown as she enjoys a night out with her sister Immy at the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 8, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Lady Gaga stripped bare! Superstar takes off make-up and changes into jeansfor raw performance of Oscar-nominated track Hold My Hand"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 117, "endOffset": 131, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 9, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Hugh Grant makes a crude joke about his appearance as he reunites with his Four Weddings And A Funeral love interest Andie MacDowell"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 120, "endOffset": 125, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Michelle Yeoh's mother Janet beams with pride and thrusts her fist in the air as she celebrates her daughter's historic Oscars win in Malaysia"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 122, "endOffset": 127, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Winnie Harlow puts on a VERY leggy display in a sweeping blush pink gown with daring split as she attends the Vanity Fair Oscars Party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 9, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 110, "endOffset": 115, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Idris Elba is joined by glamorous wife Sabrina as she stuns in a plunging shimmering dress at the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 2, "displayName": "ORG"}], "textContent": "BBC's Linekergate football boycott is OVER as Radio 5 Live's Monday Night Club show returns as normal tonight"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 95, "endOffset": 100, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Naomi Campbell, 52, puts on a daring display in a cream mermaid-style dress at the Vanity Fair Oscars afterparty"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 17, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 135, "endOffset": 140, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Alicia Silverstone dazzles in a glitzy emerald gown with a thigh high split as she joins designer Christian Siriano at the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 116, "endOffset": 121, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Cara Delevingne puts on a VERY busty display in a sheer white off-the-shoulder gown as she poses at the Vanity Fair Oscars bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 121, "endOffset": 126, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Hilary Duff cuts an elegant figure in a strapless peach gown as she joins dapper husband Matthew Koma at the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 17, "endOffset": 26, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Feeling peckish! Gigi Hadid tucks into an In-N-Out burger as she leaves the Vanity Fair Oscar bash after dazzling on the red carpet"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 4, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 49, "endOffset": 54, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Was Hugh Grant REALLY to blame for his car-crash Oscars interview? Global media blasts 'contemptuous' replies to Ashley Graham"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 58, "endOffset": 65, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 6, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Shakira keeps sons  close to her as they prepare to leave New York after singer alluded to Gerard Pique split by saying she 'put up with so much c**p'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 65, "endOffset": 74, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 86, "endOffset": 91, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "'He's famous for being like that': GMB's Susanna Reid cringes at Hugh Grant's painful Oscars chat after viewers slam actor for 'worst interview EVER'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 86, "endOffset": 91, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Awkward moment Good Morning Britain presenter is refused entry to Elton John's annual Oscars party live on air"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 19, "endOffset": 28, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 82, "endOffset": 94, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Kendall Jenner and Gigi Hadid kick off the party with a KISS as winners including Michelle Yeoh and Brendan Fraser arrive to celebrate"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Salma Hayek, 56, puts on a busty display in a plunging sequinned gown as she joins lookalike daughter Valentina Pinault, 15, at Vanity Fair's Oscar bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 89, "endOffset": 94, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Daisy Edgar-Jones is a vision as she stuns in a racy see-through gown at the Vanity Fair Oscars Party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Kate Bosworth and Justin Long spark engagement rumours as she sports a HUGE diamond ring during PDA-packed appearance"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 31, "endOffset": 40, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 53, "endOffset": 66, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 120, "endOffset": 125, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "The ULTIMATE girls' night out! Gigi Hadid, Kylie and Kendall Jenner and Lily Aldridge party together at the Vanity Fair Oscars bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 39, "endOffset": 44, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "'We spent 32 years making films and no Oscars': Richard Curtis' partner Emma Freud gets 'revenge' over her brother Matthew's win"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 8, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 79, "endOffset": 84, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Lady Gaga kisses her Folie à Deux castmate Brendan Gleeson on the lips  at the Oscars as filming for their Joker sequel continues"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 97, "endOffset": 109, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Florence Pugh wows in a tiny bralet and oversized coat as she celebrates with giddy Best Actress Michelle Yeoh at Vanity Fair's Oscar bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 123, "endOffset": 128, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Laura Harrier goes braless beneath her black sheer gown as she makes a bold red carpet statement at the annual Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 59, "endOffset": 69, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 8, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Maya Jama's most show-stopping outfits: A look back at the Love Island host's best ensembles on the show"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 37, "endOffset": 39, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 4, "endOffset": 15, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "LIVEGary Lineker row live: Fury over BBC's climbdown as MOTD host is set to return to TV screens this weekend"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 8, "endOffset": 18, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Who are Love Island 2023 finalists Ron and Lana? Everything you need to know about the PDA-shy couple after overcoming the hunk's interest in EVERY woman in the villa"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 8, "endOffset": 18, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Who are Love Island finalists Kai and Sanam? Everything you need to know about the couple who survived Olivia's wrath when romance blossomed"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 8, "endOffset": 18, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Who are Love Island 2023 finalists Tom and Samie? A look-back at the pair's turbulent romance after the terrace-loving hunk's dalliances"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 8, "endOffset": 18, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Who are Love Island 2023 finalists Shaq and Tanya? Everything you need to know about the influencer and security officer's turbulent romance"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 76, "endOffset": 85, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Kyle Walker's wife Annie is seen wearing her wedding ring as she arrives at Manchester City training ground - days after footballer 'flashed and kissed a woman in a bar'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 75, "endOffset": 83, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 104, "endOffset": 117, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Former star of The Office Rainn Wilson says there's anti-Christian bias in Hollywood after episode 8 of The Last Of Us"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 119, "endOffset": 121, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Gary Lineker 'Tweetgate' row 'will be resolved \"to his satisfaction\" within 24 hours' with a 'horrible review fudge of BBC social media guidelines'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 22, "endOffset": 32, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "The comeback kid! How Ke Huy Quan resurrected his career to win an Oscar 40 YEARS after he first rose to fame in The Goonies"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 80, "endOffset": 88, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 13, "endOffset": 24, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 45, "endOffset": 57, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 5, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Oscars 2023: Jimmy Kimmel roasts THAT  slap, Nicole Kidman's AMC deal and mocks Hollywood's obsession with weight loss drug in epic monologue"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Amy Winehouse's £3 million former home in Camden is 'plagued by Instagrammers' - with one describing it as their 'Graceland'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 26, "endOffset": 36, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 57, "endOffset": 62, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Ana De Armas proudly hugs Ke Huy Quan at the Vanity Fair Oscars party after his win for Best Supporting Actor"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 92, "endOffset": 97, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Ellie Goulding stuns in a backless figure-hugging black gown as she attends the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 41, "endOffset": 46, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Brendan Fraser celebrates his first EVER Oscars win with his sons Holden, 18, and Leland, 16, as he thrusts trophy in the air at the Vanity Fair bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 17, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Andrea Riseborough shares a tender moment with partner Karim Saleh at Vanity Fair Oscar bash after backlash over her Best Actress nomination"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 69, "endOffset": 74, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 124, "endOffset": 135, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Hailey Bieber wows in a figure-hugging black gown at the Vanity Fair Oscars bash as she makes first public appearance since Selena Gomez 'feud'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 6, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 123, "endOffset": 128, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Cardi B looks ravishing in a figure-hugging red gown as she packs on the PDA with dapper husband Offset at the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Michelle Yeoh, 60, looks sensational in a strapless woven gown as she celebrates her HISTORIC Best Actress win at Vanity Fair's annual Oscar bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 58, "endOffset": 63, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Pedro Pascal is ever the supportive brother as he attends Oscars as his nominated sister's date"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 43, "endOffset": 48, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Kate Hudson's daughter Rani, 4, holds cute Oscars viewing party with her friends and can't believe it when she sees parent taking to the stage"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 103, "endOffset": 108, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Kate Beckinsale stuns in a glittering semi-sheer gown with a dramatic sweeping cape at the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 128, "endOffset": 132, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 71, "endOffset": 76, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Austin Butler and Kaia Gerber put on a loved-up display at Vanity Fair Oscars party after he misses out on Best Actor award for Elvis"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 126, "endOffset": 131, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Kate Hudson cuts a glamorous figure in a plunging pink gown with tulle sleeves as she steps out at Vanity Fair's star-studded Oscars bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 64, "endOffset": 77, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 116, "endOffset": 128, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 5, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Oscars 2023 recap: Everything Everywhere All at Once wins SEVEN Academy Awards , Brendan Fraser bags Best Actor and Michelle Yeoh wins Best Actress"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 7, "endOffset": 18, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Inside Harry Styles' relationship with glamorous Australian fashionista Yan Yan Chan during his recent visit Down Under"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 122, "endOffset": 127, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 14, "endOffset": 25, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Newly engaged Rebel Wilson and Ramona Agruma share a passionate smooch as they make a glamorous appearance at Vanity Fair Oscars Party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 32, "endOffset": 40, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 9, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 141, "endOffset": 146, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Lily James looks every inch the Hollywood star in a sweeping powder pink evening gown as she makes a glamorous appearance at the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 119, "endOffset": 128, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 86, "endOffset": 91, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Ashley Graham flaunts her jaw-dropping figure beneath a sheer red gown at Vanity Fair Oscars bash - after THAT awkward Hugh Grant interview"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 125, "endOffset": 130, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Eva Longoria flashes her toned pins in a slinky semi-sheer black gown as she makes a glamorous appearance at the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 95, "endOffset": 100, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Zoe Saldana leaves little to the imagination as she goes braless in a sheer top at Vanity Fair Oscars bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 105, "endOffset": 117, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 89, "endOffset": 94, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Phoebe Tonkin dazzles in a glittering gold and black gown as she attends the Vanity Fair Oscars Party in Beverly Hills alongside Hailee Steinfeld"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 119, "endOffset": 124, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Perfect match: Sophie Turner and husband Joe Jonas both wear black as they co-ordinate glamorous looks for Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 132, "endOffset": 137, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Jodie Turner-Smith competes for best dressed in an elegant form-fitting gown as she joins husband Joshua Jackson at the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 35, "endOffset": 47, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 100, "endOffset": 110, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Indiana Jones reunion 39 years on! Harrison Ford shares poignant hug with Temple of Doom child star Ke Huy Quan amid his epic comeback"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 79, "endOffset": 91, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Morgan Freeman wears a satin glove on his paralyzed hand  as he presents  with Margot Robbie - 15 years after car accident left him seriously injured"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 124, "endOffset": 132, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Keeping up with the Jenners! Kylie and Kendall enjoy a night of sibling revelry in flirty frocks as they rub shoulders with Hollywood's A-list"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 114, "endOffset": 126, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Sharon Stone, 65, cuts a youthful figure in elegant caped gown as she attends the 2023 Vanity Fair Oscar party in Beverly Hills"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 108, "endOffset": 121, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Troye Sivan rocks an eye-popping corset and pinstriped suit at the Elton John AIDS Foundation's 31st Annual Academy Awards Viewing Party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 15, "endOffset": 25, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Baring it ALL! Halle Berry leads the worst dressed stars in bizarre tulle ensemble at Vanity Fair's Oscar party - while Ashley Graham opts for revealing kaftan"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 21, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 76, "endOffset": 91, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Married At First Sight's Martha Kalifatidis shares adorable video of fiancé Michael Brunelli doting on their newborn son as she pumps breastmilk"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 56, "endOffset": 67, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 15, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 44, "endOffset": 49, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Malala Yousafzai's dad says she 'outwitted' Oscars host Jimmy Kimmel - and jokes his activist daughter is 'clever like her mum'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 46, "endOffset": 55, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 83, "endOffset": 94, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 33, "endOffset": 38, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "The unforgettable moments of the Oscars 2023: Hugh Grant's very awkward interview, Jimmy Kimmel's slap joke, Angela Bassett's snub and a donkey"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 86, "endOffset": 97, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "The award for the raciest dress goes to... Emily Ratajkowski, Alessandra Ambrosio and Olivia Wilde bare all in a parade of risqué looks at Vanity Fair"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 4, "endOffset": 14, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 108, "endOffset": 116, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "LIVELove Island Final 2023 LIVE: Fans gear up to see who will WIN the winter series in South Africa as host Maya Jama gets ready for presenting duties"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 18, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Kourtney Kardashian is a blonde beauty as she poses in a black off-the-shoulder gown and matching gloves"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 14, "endOffset": 22, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Love Island's Maya Jama wears under-eye patches and sports unkempt hair ahead of a makeover as she gets ready to host the live final in South Africa"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 54, "endOffset": 67, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'The luck of the Irish was with us as the sun shone': Pierce Brosnan shares selfie with his wife Keely Shaye Smith as he wraps filming in Northern Ireland"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 111, "endOffset": 113, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 42, "endOffset": 53, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 94, "endOffset": 100, "displayName": "ORG"}], "textContent": "'We remain a country of tolerant people': Gary Lineker shares pointed statement after migrant Twitter storm as BBC bosses bring him back to MOTD"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 120, "endOffset": 126, "displayName": "ORG"}], "textContent": "Michelle Keegan beams while sipping on coffee as she gets into character as ex special ops pilot Maya on the set of new Netflix drama Fool Me Once"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 16, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Jennifer Coolidge, 61, continues looking sensational after a night of partying as she heads home from Vanity Fair's star-studded Oscar bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 40, "endOffset": 45, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Anne Heche and Charlbi Dean left out of Oscars' in memoriam segment"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 19, "endOffset": 35, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 87, "endOffset": 92, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Joshua Jackson and Michelle Williams have a mini Dawson's Creek reunion at Vanity Fair Oscars Party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 85, "endOffset": 90, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Charli XCX channels gothic chic in a corset top and buckled skirt at the Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 10, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Love Island SPOILER: Four final couples get a dance lesson before penning declarations of love as Tom has something big to share ahead of finale"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 133, "endOffset": 146, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 25, "endOffset": 37, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 17, "endOffset": 22, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 59, "endOffset": 69, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Offspring at the Oscars! Colin Farrell, Brendan Fraser and Salma Hayek prove their kids are the ultimate red carpet accessory at the Academy Awards"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 9, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 43, "endOffset": 48, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Hugh Grant shuts down Ashley Graham at the Oscars 2023 and rolls his eyes in a very awkward red carpet chat with the presenter leaving fans 'cringing'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 116, "endOffset": 131, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'Sore loser is never a good look!' Angela Bassett's crestfallen reaction to losing Best Supporting Actress Oscar to Jamie Lee Curtis goes viral"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 3, "endOffset": 15, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "As Michelle Yeoh, 60, wins her first-ever Academy Award, FEMAIL reveals how she rose from being an aspiring ballerina and beauty queen"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 49, "endOffset": 57, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 104, "endOffset": 109, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 72, "endOffset": 78, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "And the award for the most risqué dress goes to! Lady Gaga and pregnant Rihanna bring sheer madness  to Oscars alongside best dressed bombshells"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 32, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 82, "endOffset": 92, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 64, "endOffset": 76, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 40, "endOffset": 45, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 158, "endOffset": 166, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Everything Everywhere All At Once rules Oscars with seven wins! Michelle Yeoh and Ke Huy Quan win with film as Best Picture while Brendan Fraser triumphs for The Whale"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 122, "endOffset": 127, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Colin Farrell and his 13-year-old son Henry Tadeusz match in dapper black tuxedos on the champagne-coloured carpet at the Oscars 2023"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 8, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Endeavour pays tribute to the late John Thaw who played the original Morse with a touching scene in the final moments of the last ever episode"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 21, "endOffset": 32, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 7, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Jon Hamm and fiancée Anna Osceola make chic couple at the Vanity Fair Oscar Party on first red carpet since confirming their engagement"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 8, "endOffset": 23, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 48, "endOffset": 53, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Tearful Jamie Lee Curtis gets emotional at 2023 Oscars accepting Best Supporting Actress honors and mentions her movie star parents were both nominated"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 109, "endOffset": 121, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 51, "endOffset": 55, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Sienna Miller is a breath of fresh air in a floral Fendi dress as she attends the Vanity Fair Oscar Party in Beverly Hills"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 100, "endOffset": 110, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 148, "endOffset": 153, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Florence Pugh and Cara Delevingne put on VERY leggy displays as they join  Phoebe Waller Bridge and Emily Blunt in leading the British stars at the Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 48, "endOffset": 55, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 98, "endOffset": 108, "displayName": "GPE"}, {"startOffset": 82, "endOffset": 87, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Naomi Watts dazzles in a figure-hugging $11,400 Givenchy dress at the Vanity Fair Oscars Party in Los Angeles"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 9, "endOffset": 15, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Pregnant Rihanna dazzles in bejeweled ensemble for moving performance of Oscar-nominated track Lift Me Up - as proud boyfriend A$AP Rocky cheers her on"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 128, "endOffset": 133, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Sarah Paulson brings back the Eighties in sequin gown with bold shoulders as she joins girlfriend Holland Taylor at Vanity Fair Oscars party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 122, "endOffset": 127, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Cocaine Bear director Elizabeth Banks apologizes for losing her voice after tripping on her own dress while presenting at Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 72, "endOffset": 85, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 90, "endOffset": 98, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Danai Gurira stands tall with towering updo while attending 95th annual Academy Awards in Hollywood"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 64, "endOffset": 77, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 20, "endOffset": 25, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Ruth Carter at 2023 Oscars becomes first Black woman to win two Academy Awards for Black Panther films"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Sofia Vergara flaunts her hourglass figure in sequined mermaid dress while posing next to husband Joe Manganiello at Vanity Fair Oscar Party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 144, "endOffset": 159, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Michael B. Jordan gives Angela Bassett a shout-out while presenting with Jonathan Majors... after she lost Oscar for Best Supporting Actress to Jamie Lee Curtis"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 118, "endOffset": 127, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Sandra Bullock, 58, is seen for the first time in ONE YEAR at an event as she flashes cleavage at pre-Oscar bash with Demi Moore and Brendan Fraser"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 51, "endOffset": 56, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 20, "endOffset": 29, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Maverick goes AWOL! Tom Cruise will NOT attend the Oscars tonight despite Top Gun sequel being favorite for Best Picture"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 118, "endOffset": 123, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 20, "endOffset": 26, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Here's my plus one! Rihanna proudly rubs her baby bump as she wows in dominatrix-style sheer leather look on the 2023 Oscars red carpet"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 11, "endOffset": 19, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Here comes Lady Gaga to the rescue! Oscar-nominated singer swoops in to help photographer after he tripped and FELL on the red carpet"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 105, "endOffset": 118, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Emma Watson looks effortlessly chic in a black bardot maxi dress as she attends Elton John's 31st Annual Academy Awards Viewing Party"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 138, "endOffset": 148, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Christina Hendricks, Heidi Klum and country singer Maren Morris lead the glamour at Elton John's 31st star-studded Oscar viewing party in Los Angeles"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 20, "endOffset": 33, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 71, "endOffset": 81, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 98, "endOffset": 103, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Parents' night out! Chrissy Teigen wows in feathery dress as she joins John Legend at Vanity Fair Oscars party two months after birth of baby Esti"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 85, "endOffset": 90, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Barry Keoghan slips into a stylish lilac suit and white bow tie as he arrives at the Oscars 2023 with partner Alyson Kierans for his first nomination"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 116, "endOffset": 121, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Va va voom! Eva Longoria puts cleavage on show in extreme V-neck dress as she poses on champagne-coloured carpet at Oscars 2023"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 22, "endOffset": 32, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 38, "endOffset": 53, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 136, "endOffset": 141, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 10, "endOffset": 19, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Who needs Will Smith? Halle Berry and Jessica Chastain step up to present best actor category after King Richard winner was BANNED from Oscars  after THAT slap"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 144, "endOffset": 146, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 28, "endOffset": 39, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "They think it's all over... Gary Lineker 'on brink of Tweetgate victory' with deal involving social media guideline changes 'to be announced by BBC today'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 110, "endOffset": 115, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Florence Pugh puts on a VERY leggy display in a cream ruched Valentino gown with tiny black underskirt on the Oscars red carpet"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 105, "endOffset": 120, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Kate and Camilla battle against blustery wind as it plays havoc with their headwear when they arrive for Commonwealth Day Service"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 133, "endOffset": 139, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 143, "endOffset": 148, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 9, "endOffset": 15, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Pregnant Rihanna flaunts her bump in a Valentino co-ord for her FOURTH tum-flashing outfit of the night as she leads the arrivals at Beyoncé's Oscars bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 91, "endOffset": 93, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 32, "endOffset": 43, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 61, "endOffset": 69, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "DAN WOOTTON: By capitulating to Gary Lineker, toothless boss Tim Davie has just signed the BBC's death warrant. It's time to defund this biased joke"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 22, "endOffset": 31, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 16, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 49, "endOffset": 54, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Leonardo DiCaprio and Gigi Hadid attend the same Oscars afterparty amid dating rumors... as model departs party in SLIPPERS"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 18, "endOffset": 30, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 131, "endOffset": 136, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "'My jaw dropped!' Nicole Kidman sends fans wild as she sassily flicks her hair and fiercely poses for the camera while working the Oscars carpet"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 38, "endOffset": 46, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 129, "endOffset": 134, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "'You have enough money for Vaseline!' Lady Gaga's chapped lips take over social media after her stripped back performance at the Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 64, "endOffset": 77, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 45, "endOffset": 58, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "It's not quite a palace! The Crown recreates Prince William and Kate Middleton moving into a shared house at university - and celebrating with a hug"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 20, "endOffset": 24, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 77, "endOffset": 83, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'He is in TROUBLE!' Adele gives Gerard Piqué a warning after watching his ex Shakira perform THAT breakup hit for the first time"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 128, "endOffset": 141, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 42, "endOffset": 53, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Colin Farrell has the perfect response to Jimmy Kimmel after quick-witted star's Irish accent is played for laughs at the 95th  Academy Awards"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 46, "endOffset": 54, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "The cat who got the cream! Beaming Duchess of Edinburgh stuns in a matching hat and coat dress as she joins Prince Edward and other royals"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 2, "displayName": "ORG"}], "textContent": "BBC Radio 4 reveal public can apply to be guest editors on Today programme instead of celebrities for the first time"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 9, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 118, "endOffset": 131, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 98, "endOffset": 103, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Kelly Ripa, 52, shows off her very toned and tanned backside in a racy black gown as she hits the Oscars with husband Mark Consuelos"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 16, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 66, "endOffset": 71, "displayName": "EVENT"}, {"startOffset": 47, "endOffset": 55, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Denzel Washington and his He Got Game director Spike Lee skip the Oscars to attend the Lakers vs. Knicks game"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 23, "endOffset": 28, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Malala's VERY handsome Oscars date! Privately-educated cricket executive Asser Malik once worked at Coca-Cola"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 7, "endOffset": 20, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "Inside Dancing On Ice's boozy wrap party: Patsy Palmer takes over the DJ decks as stars hit the dancefloor at raucous bash"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 78, "endOffset": 80, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 65, "endOffset": 76, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 37, "endOffset": 52, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "'There's something nice about that!' Holly Willoughby wades into Gary Lineker BBC tweet row as she praises his colleagues for showing solidarity"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 13, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 69, "endOffset": 74, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Kendall Jenner and Bad Bunny continue to fuel romance rumors leaving Oscars after-party at Chateau Marmont in the SAME car"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 4, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"startOffset": 41, "endOffset": 57, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Elvis's Memphis mansion Graceland DENIES Priscilla Presley was 'locked out by granddaughter Riley Keough amid fallout over Lisa Marie's  will"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 113, "endOffset": 128, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Kate and Camilla battle against blustery wind playing havoc with their headwear as they're joined by Geri Horner Commonwealth Day Service"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 55, "endOffset": 70, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Geri Horner looks chic in an all-white ensemble at the Commonwealth Day Service after being appointed inaugural ambassador"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Selena Gomez would be 'crying my eyes out' over body shaming comments despite portraying herself as someone who didn't care: 'I lied'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 134, "endOffset": 143, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 115, "endOffset": 128, "displayName": "PERSON"}, {"startOffset": 59, "endOffset": 60, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Justin Bieber arrives at the Vanity Fair Oscar party in a BLANKET to join wife Hailey Bieber who parties with pals Kendall Jenner and Gigi Hadid"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 115, "endOffset": 121, "displayName": "ORG"}], "textContent": "Georgina Rodriguez puts on a busty display in red bodycon as she gives fans a glimpse of 'shooting day' - ahead of Netflix show release"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 123, "endOffset": 128, "displayName": "EVENT"}], "textContent": "Emma Watson looks ethereal in a sheer lace gown before changing into a plunging black dress in a photoshoot after the 2023 Oscars"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 9, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Blac Chyna, 34, undergoes breast and butt reductions as part of her 'life changing journey': 'I'm passing the baton to the younger ladies'"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 91, "endOffset": 99, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "The King and I! Charles enjoys a touching moment with his sister-in-law Sophie, Duchess of Edinburgh during the Commonwealth service"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 12, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Kyle Richards, 54, is slender in a dress she 'stole' from her daughter when at an Oscar party as she again denies using Ozempic"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 44, "endOffset": 53, "displayName": "WORK_OF_ART"}], "textContent": "'You are a freaking queen worthy of love!': EastEnders star Melissa Suffield exudes confidence as she slips into lingerie for empowering post"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 47, "endOffset": 55, "displayName": "GPE"}], "textContent": "Sophie's cream of the crop! Beaming Duchess of Edinburgh stuns in a matching hat and coat dress as she joins Prince Edward and other royals"}
{"textSegmentAnnotations": [{"startOffset": 34, "endOffset": 36, "displayName": "ORG"}, {"startOffset": 0, "endOffset": 11, "displayName": "PERSON"}], "textContent": "Gary Lineker row RECAP: Fury over BBC's climbdown as MOTD host is set to return to TV screens this weekend"}
